

Graphic Designer
Jakarta, Indonesia
azzamhamiludin@gmail.com
+60 1112781576

PROFILE

5+ years of experience in the graphic design world (Autodidact). Ex-COO of PolusMedia Sdn. Bhd. Hungry for knowledge, design enthusiast and high willingness to help others in need. Loves to tackle challenges using as much critical thinking and brain power as possible.

WORK EXPERIENCE

COO of PolusMedia, Self-Employed, Johor Bahru, Malaysia

JUNE 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Head of Multimedia and Publications Department of ISS Indonesia, ISS Indonesia, Johor Bahru, Malaysia

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

EDUCATION

CKILLC

Software Engineering, Universiti Teknologi Malaysia, Johor Bahru, Malaysia

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2024

Current CGPA of 3.35

Adobe Lightroom	Microsoft Office
Adobe After Effects	Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe Illustrator	Adobe Photoshop
HOBBIES Games, Computer, Design Graphic, Making	Money
LANGUAGES	
English	Bahasa
Malay	

www.azzamhamiludin.com

LINKS